<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Londopedia</string>
    <string name="explore_button">Let\'s Explore</string>

    <!-- Main categories -->
    <string name="category_transportation">Transportation</string>
    <string name="category_bridge">Bridge</string>
    <string name="category_attraction">Attraction</string>
    <string name="category_park">Park</string>

    <!-- sub category lists of Transportation -->
    <string name="transportation_underground">Underground</string>
    <string name="transportation_bus">Bus</string>
    <string name="transportation_taxi">Taxi</string>
    <string name="transportation_dlr">Docklands Light Railway</string>
    <string name="transportation_cycle">Cycling</string>
    <string name="transportation_airways">Airways</string>

    <!-- sub category lists of Bridge -->
    <string name="bridge_tower_bridge">Tower Bridge</string>
    <string name="bridge_westminster_bridge">Westminster Bridge</string>
    <string name="bridge_london_eye">London Eye</string>
    <string name="bridge_shard">The Shard</string>

    <!-- sub category lists of Park -->
    <string name="park_hyde">Hyde Park</string>
    <string name="park_regents">Regent\'s Park</string>
    <string name="park_richmond">Richmond Park</string>
    <string name="park_greenwich">Greenwich Park</string>

    <!-- sub category lists of Attraction -->
    <string name="attraction_tower_of_london">Tower of London</string>
    <string name="attraction_buckingham_palace">Buckingham Palace</string>
    <string name="attraction_westminster_abbey">Westminster Abbey</string>
    <string name="attraction_paul_cathedral">St.Paul\'s Cathedral</string>
    <string name="attraction_big_ben">Big Ben</string>
    <string name="attraction_windsor_castle">Windsor Castle</string>

    <!-- Attractions establishment days -->
    <string name="london_tower_established">%S 1066</string>
    <string name="buckingham_palace_established">%S 1703</string>
    <string name="westminster_abbey_established">%S 960 AD</string>
    <string name="st_pauls_cathedral_established">%S 1675 \- 1710</string>
    <string name="big_ben_established">%S 1840</string>
    <string name="windsor_castle_established">%S 1070</string>

    <!-- Parks establishment days -->
    <string name="hyde_park_established">%S 1637</string>
    <string name="regents_park_established">%S 1811</string>
    <string name="richmond_park_established">%S 1625</string>
    <string name="greenwich_park_established">%S 1433</string>

    <!-- Main categories descriptions -->
    <string name="category_transportation_description">London has a well-connected transport system,
        including the Underground (Tube), buses, and trains.
        The Oyster card makes travel easy across the city.
    </string>
    <string name="category_bridge_description">London\'s bridges, like Tower Bridge and London Bridge,
        connect the city across the River Thames.
        They are iconic landmarks blending history and modern engineering.
    </string>
    <string name="category_attraction_description">London is rich in history, featuring landmarks like the Tower of London,
        Buckingham Palace, and Big Ben. These sites showcase the city\'s royal heritage and architectural beauty.
    </string>
    <string name="category_park_description">London has many beautiful parks, including Hyde Park, Regent\'s Park,
        and Greenwich Park. They offer green spaces for relaxation, walking, and outdoor activities.
    </string>

    <!-- Transportation's sub category list description -->
    <string name="transportation_underground_description">The London Underground is the world’s first metro system, operating since 1863.
        With 11 lines and 270 stations, it’s the quickest way to navigate the city.
    </string>
    <string name="transportation_taxi_description">London’s Black Cabs are world-famous and driven by professionals who pass
        "The Knowledge" test,ensuring they know every street in London.
    </string>
    <string name="transportation_dlr_description">The DLR is an automated light railway that serves East London, connecting
        areas like Greenwich, Canary Wharf, and London City Airport.
    </string>
    <string name="transportation_cycling_description">London has dedicated cycling lanes and the Santander Cycles (Boris Bikes) system,
        where you can rent a bike from docking stations around the city.
    </string>
    <string name="transportation_airways_description">London is served by major airports like Heathrow, Gatwick, and Stansted.
        They connect the city to destinations worldwide with numerous flights daily.
    </string>

    <!-- Bridge's sub category list description -->
    <string name="bridge_tower_bridge_description">One of London’s most famous landmarks, Tower Bridge is a symbol of the city. Built in 1894,
        this bascule and suspension bridge features two towers connected by a glass walkway, offering stunning views of the Thames.
    </string>
    <string name="bridge_westminster_bridge_description">One of the most scenic bridges in London, Westminster Bridge offers stunning views of Big Ben,
        the Houses of Parliament, and the London Eye. It’s a must-visit for first-time travelers.
    </string>
    <string name="bridge_london_eye_description">The South Bank is home to The London Eye, offering one of the best panoramic views of the city.
        This riverside area is packed with street performers, restaurants, and cultural attractions.
    </string>
    <string name="bridge_shard_description">For the ultimate cityscape view, visit The View from The Shard. At 310 meters high, it’s the tallest
        building in Western Europe.
    </string>

    <!-- Park's sub category list description -->
    <string name="park_hyde_description">One of London’s largest and most famous parks, Hyde Park spans 350 acres and is a hub for both relaxation and activities.
        Originally a hunting ground for King Henry VIII, it is now a public park filled with beautiful gardens,
        lakes, and walking paths. It is also a center for political debates at Speaker’s Corner and home to concerts,
        events, and festivals throughout the year.
    </string>
    <string name="park_regent_description">Designed by John Nash, Regent’s Park is one of the most beautifully landscaped parks in London. It covers 395 acres and is
        home to lush gardens, scenic walkways, and diverse wildlife. It’s also the site of London Zoo,
        the world’s oldest scientific zoo.
    </string>
    <string name="park_richmond_description">Originally created as a royal hunting ground for King Charles I, Richmond Park is now London’s largest royal park, covering 2,500 acres.
        It is a designated National Nature Reserve, known for its free-roaming herds of deer and breathtaking landscapes.
    </string>
    <string name="park_greenwich_description">A UNESCO World Heritage Site, Greenwich Park is one of London’s oldest and most historic parks.
        It was once a hunting ground for Henry VIII and now offers stunning city views, beautiful gardens, and historical landmarks.
    </string>

    <!-- Attraction's sub category list description -->
    <string name="attraction_tower_of_london_description">The Tower of London is one of the most famous castles in the world, with over 1,000 years of history. Originally built as a fortress
        by William the Conqueror, it later served as a royal palace, prison, armory, treasury, and even a zoo!
    </string>
    <string name="attraction_buckingham_palace_description">Buckingham Palace is the administrative headquarters of the monarchy and a symbol of Britain’s royal heritage. It has 775 rooms,
        including 52 royal bedrooms, 92 offices, and a 40-acre garden—the largest private garden in London!
    </string>
    <string name="attraction_westminster_abbey_description">A UNESCO World Heritage Site, Westminster Abbey has been the coronation church for British monarchs since 1066. It has hosted 16
        royal weddings and is the final resting place of over 3,300 people, including kings, queens, poets, and scientists.
    </string>
    <string name="attraction_paul_cathedral_description">One of the most iconic buildings in London, St. Paul’s Cathedral was designed by Sir Christopher Wren after
        the Great Fire of London in 1666. The cathedral is famous for its huge dome, which was inspired by St. Peter’s Basilica in Rome.
    </string>
    <string name="attraction_big_ben_description">The Palace of Westminster is home to the UK Parliament and features one of the most recognizable clock towers
        in the world, Big Ben (officially called the Elizabeth Tower).
    </string>
    <string name="attraction_windsor_castle_description">Windsor Castle has been a royal residence for over 900 years and remains an official home of the British
        monarchy. It is a working palace, often used for royal ceremonies.
    </string>

    <!-- Key Feature of transportation -->
    <!-- Underground -->
    <string name="underground_point_1">%S Oyster Card &amp; Contactless Payment accepted</string>
    <string name="underground_point_2">%S Zones 1–6 (Central London = Zone 1)</string>
    <string name="underground_point_3">%S Night Tube (operates on weekends on select lines)</string>
    <!-- Bus -->
    <string name="bus_point_1">Flat fare of £1.75 per journey (unlimited transfers within an hour)</string>
    <string name="bus_point_2">Contactless &amp; Oyster Card payments only (no cash)</string>
    <string name="bus_point_3">Best routes for sightseeing:</string>
    <string name="bus_point_4">Route 11 (Big Ben, St Paul’s, Tower of London)</string>
    <string name="bus_point_5">Route 24 (Westminster, Camden, Hampstead Heath)</string>
    <!-- Taxi -->
    <string name="taxi_point_1">Can be hailed on the street or booked via apps</string>
    <string name="taxi_point_2">Fares based on distance &amp; time</string>
    <string name="taxi_point_3">Uber &amp; Bolt also operate in London</string>
    <!-- DLR -->
    <string name="dlr_point_1">Fully automated, no driver</string>
    <string name="dlr_point_2">Connects to the Tube network</string>
    <string name="dlr_point_3">Great views of London Docklands</string>
    <!-- Cycling -->
    <string name="cycling_point_1">Rent a bike for just £2 for 24 hours</string>
    <string name="cycling_point_2">First 30 minutes free per ride</string>
    <string name="cycling_point_3">Docking stations available across the city</string>
    <!-- Airways -->
    <string name="airways_point_1">Heathrow Express (fastest way to Central London)</string>
    <string name="airways_point_2">Gatwick Express &amp; Thameslink (fastest for Gatwick)</string>
    <string name="airways_point_3">Stansted Express (best for Stansted Airport)</string>

    <!-- Key Feature of Bridge -->
    <!-- Tower Bridge -->
    <string name="tower_bridge_point_1">Glass Floor Walkway (42 meters above the river)</string>
    <string name="tower_bridge_point_2">Engine Rooms (historic steam engines that once powered the bridge)</string>
    <string name="tower_bridge_point_3">Scenic views of the Tower of London &amp; The Shard</string>
    <!-- Westminster Bridge -->
    <string name="westminster_bridge_point_1">Best selfie spot with Big Ben</string>
    <string name="westminster_bridge_point_2">Short walk to Westminster Abbey &amp; St James’s Park</string>
    <string name="westminster_bridge_point_3">Great place for sunset views</string>
    <!-- London Eye -->
    <string name="london_eye_point_1">The London Eye (Europe’s tallest observation wheel)</string>
    <string name="london_eye_point_2">The Southbank Centre (art &amp; music venue)</string>
    <string name="london_eye_point_3">Amazing night views along the Thames</string>
    <!-- The Shard -->
    <string name="shard_point_1">Unbeatable skyline views</string>
    <string name="shard_point_2">Cocktail bar on the 72nd floor</string>
    <string name="shard_point_3">Glass balconies with open-air experience</string>

    <!-- Key Feature of Park -->
    <!-- Hyde Park -->
    <string name="hyde_point_1">The Serpentine Lake, great for boating and swimming</string>
    <string name="hyde_point_2">Diana Memorial Fountain, dedicated to Princess Diana</string>
    <string name="hyde_point_3">Winter Wonderland, a magical Christmas festival in December</string>
    <!-- Regent's Park -->
    <string name="regent_point_1">Queen Mary’s Rose Garden, with over 12,000 roses 🌹</string>
    <string name="regent_point_2">Regent’s Canal, where you can take a boat ride to Camden Market</string>
    <string name="regent_point_3">Open Air Theatre, hosting live performances in the summer</string>
    <!-- Richmond Park -->
    <string name="richmond_point_1">The Deer Park, home to over 600 red and fallow deer</string>
    <string name="richmond_point_2">Isabella Plantation, a stunning woodland garden 🌺</string>
    <string name="richmond_point_3">King Henry’s Mound, with a distant view of St. Paul’s Cathedral</string>
    <!-- Greenwich Park -->
    <string name="greenwich_point_1">The Royal Observatory, where Greenwich Mean Time (GMT) is set</string>
    <string name="greenwich_point_2">The Prime Meridian Line, where you can stand in two hemispheres at once</string>
    <string name="greenwich_point_3">Greenwich Hill, offering the best panoramic view of the London skyline</string>

    <!-- Key Feature of Attraction -->
    <!-- Tower of London -->
    <string name="london_tower_point_1">The Crown Jewels, including the Imperial State Crown 💎</string>
    <string name="london_tower_point_2">The Bloody Tower, where the two Princes mysteriously disappeared</string>
    <string name="london_tower_point_3">The Ravens of the Tower, believed to protect the monarchy</string>
    <!-- Buckingham Palace -->
    <string name="buckingham_point_1">Changing of the Guard Ceremony (daily in summer, alternate days in winter)</string>
    <string name="buckingham_point_2">The Throne Room, used for royal ceremonies</string>
    <string name="buckingham_point_3">The Queen’s Gallery, displaying royal art collections</string>
    <!-- Westminster Abbey -->
    <string name="westminster_abbey_point_1">Poet’s Corner, burial site of Shakespeare, Chaucer, and Dickens</string>
    <string name="westminster_abbey_point_2">The Coronation Chair, used in every coronation since 1308</string>
    <string name="westminster_abbey_point_3">Tomb of the Unknown Warrior, dedicated to soldiers of World War I</string>
    <!-- St Paul's Cathedral -->
    <string name="paul_cathedral_point_1">The Whispering Gallery, where sound travels along the curved walls</string>
    <string name="paul_cathedral_point_2">The Golden Gallery, with stunning panoramic views of London</string>
    <string name="paul_cathedral_point_3">Crypt, containing tombs of Lord Nelson and Sir Christopher Wren</string>
    <!-- Big Ben -->
    <string name="big_ben_point_1">House of Commons &amp; House of Lords, where British laws are debated</string>
    <string name="big_ben_point_2">Clock Tower, standing 96 meters (316 feet) tall</string>
    <string name="big_ben_point_3">Nighttime Illuminations, making the gothic architecture stand out</string>
    <!-- Windsor Castle -->
    <string name="windsor_castle_point_1">St. George’s Chapel, where Prince Harry &amp; Meghan Markle got married</string>
    <string name="windsor_castle_point_2">The Long Walk, a stunning 3-mile avenue leading to the castle</string>
    <string name="windsor_castle_point_3">The State Apartments, with lavish royal decor</string>

    <string name="right_arrow">Right Arrow</string>
    <string name="back_arrow">Back Arrow</string>
    <string name="additional_information">Additional Information</string>
</resources>